in a couple years nobody is going to
call him sm's husband they'll call me
Jonathan Owen's wife speaking of bless
her heart you know what's crazy and dope
and amazing is that we can all live in
our dope amazingness without having to
diminish ourselves to show the dopeness
and amazingness of our partner and the
feeling that you got to do that
sometimes don't even got nothing to do
with your partner and everything to do
with Society or your upbringing or your
surroundings etc etc but I want to Here
and Now say unequivocally without
question that this 26-year-old Phenom is
the greatest gymnast of all time like
literally in the history of the sport
thus we should give all the props and
being that does not make her any less of
a great wife to this person who is
someone that plays football